* For who
* Product

Privacy Statement
=================

25-07-2023

This privacy statement is applicable to all visits on our website ([www.secretview.io](http://www.secretview.io/)) and our platform ([https://platform.secretview.io](https://platform.secretview.io/)), the mobile application, the agreement existing between you and us when you are registered to our platform as a community member, as well as the assignments you do as a mystery shopper. By visiting the website and/or the platform, you agree to this statement. Changes in this statement will be valid as soon as they are applied (see Last updated above). When this statement changes, we will publish a notification on the platform.

We, Secret Collect B.V., called “**Secret View**” hereafter, are responsible for processing personal data as described in this privacy statement. Our contact details are:

Velperplein 23A

6811 AH Arnhem

CoC no.: 62351761

Phone: +31 26 - 20 22 151

E-mail: [support@secretview.io](mailto:support@secretview.io)

This privacy statement was originally written in Dutch. In the event a translation of this privacy statement conflicts with the Dutch original version, the original version will always take precedence. This privacy statement may be modified by Secret View at any moment.

Should you have any questions and/or remarks about this privacy statement, please contact us via the live chat or via [mysteryshopping@secretview.io](mailto:mysteryshopping@secretview.io).

**Short version**

We value your privacy and strive to protect it. In this privacy statement we’ll explain which personal data is collected and why it is being processed. The (personal) data we process will never be shared with third parties without your explicit prior consent. You’ll find the highlights in this short summary, but we recommend you read the full version carefully.

We collect all information, including personal data, that you provide us with. Aside from that, we also store technical information like cookies to make sure you experience on the website and the platform is as comfortable and personal as possible. All data is stored in secured servers that are not accessible to unauthorized personnel.

The platform uses several technological mechanisms to automate our processes. This includes automated decision-making based on profile and experience. An example of this is the eligibility of a mystery shopper for a certain assignment.

If you would like to exercise your right to object and/or your right to data portability, or do you have any other questions about our data processing? Please contact us with a specific request at [support@secretview.io](mailto:support@secretview.io).

**Long version**

We process data from the following groups:

1. Visitors of our website [www.secretview.io](http://www.secretview.io/);
2. People registered as mystery shoppers with Secret View;
3. Contacts of Secret View’s clients.

Below we will outline per group the personal data we process and why we do so.

1. **Website visitors**

We process visitors’ personal data on our website [www.secretview.io](http://www.secretview.io/) by placing cookies and similar technologies such as web beacons.

A cookie is a small text file that is stored in your computer’s browser, tablet or smartphone when you first visit the website. We use functional, analytical and tracking cookies. On your first visit, we’ve informed you of these cookies and asked for your permission to store them in your browser. Please find all information about our cookies in our Cookie Policy.

1. **Community members**

When you register as a community member on our platform, you engage in an agreement with us. To carry out this agreement, e.g., do mystery shopping research, it is necessary for us to process some of your personal data. We’ll sum up the data we process:

\-          Name

\-          Sex

\-          Date of birth

\-          Address

\-          Phone number

\-          E-mail address

\-          Other data that is actively provided by creating a profile, in writing or by phone

\-          Location details

\-          Banking details

\-          Financial remunerations

Without these details we are unable to hold our part of the agreement. In order to fulfill our legal and societal duties we will process data in the event of (suspected) cases of illegal activities by members of our community and provide them to authorities. Also, we store verified addresses by using iDIN ([https://www.idin.nl/disclaimer-privacy/](https://www.idin.nl/disclaimer-privacy/)) in order to be able to take legal action in the event of illegal activities.

**Why do we process personal data?**

We process your personal data to:

\-          Allow you to create an online account

\-          Assign one or more mystery shopping assignments to you

\-          Communicate with you in relation to the assignments

\-          Handle payments

\-          Verify your age when you apply for an age-related assignment that legally requires us to verify your age (e.g. alcohol and tobacco sales compliance research)

\-          Analyze user behavior on our website and platform to improve our online tools and to adapt our services to your preferences

\-          Being able to create analyses and anonymized statistics on the basis of your age, income and other data you have shared with us, that helps us inform our clients (for example: “mystery shoppers between 40- and 45-years old rate your store the highest”);

\-          Follow up on complaints and questions

\-          Carry out legal duties or court rulings, such as providing data for tax returns

\-          Preventing misuse and abuse

**What else do we do with your data?**

To make your experience as a mystery shopper as good as possible, your data is saved in your online account. This way you won’t need to enter your data repeatedly.

**Community Approval**

The results from our researches go through a quality control before they are validated and sent to our clients. This approval process is carried out by Secret View employees, but also by other members of the community (mystery shoppers). Community members with this capacity are called Community Approvers and are carefully selected by us. Therefore, it is possible that another community member gets to view the questionnaire you send in. We take every possible step to decrease the chance a Community Approver gets insight into personal data. Your questionnaire is anonymized and there is a blackout tool that can be used to blur out certain sections. However, you are personally responsible for the information you provide textually in your answers about yourself or other people in describing certain situations. The Community Approver can edit and/or improve the answers you provide.

**Automated decision-making**

Using automated decision-making processes allows us to more efficiently handle large numbers of (mystery shopping) assignments. These automated processes may have consequences for registered community members regarding planning and/or carrying out assignments. The processes lead to decision made by computer programs or systems without human (i.e., a Secret View employee) interference/involvement.

We use the following computer programs and systems:

Name:

Self-developed software

Why do we use it?

The software we develop in-house is used to make carrying out research and insights into its results as efficient and user-friendly as possible.

What automated process take place in the software?

The following processes may be (to some extent) automated:

* Profile and account management
* Insight into all assignments
* Selection of mystery shoppers
* Insight into assignment status
* Information supply for assignments
* Handling payments

To make the transition period from manual to automated processes as smooth as possible, every automation (process, decision-making, specific actions) is first rolled out in phases. The automated process, decision or action will first be shown to the employee and/or user, who will manually have to confirm the event. Only when we are sure the automation works as intended at all times, we will allow the automation to take place without human interference. Using this method, we make sure users will not notice the transition from manual to automation – except for the efficiency and user-friendliness increases.

As a community member, you have the right to voice your opinion with regards to an automated decision that involves you, and to object to this decision. If you do not agree with an automated decision, please feel free to contact us. An employee will manually review the decision. By agreeing to carry out assignments (and our Terms & Conditions and this Privacy Policy), you explicitly agree with the use of automated decision-making processes in our platform.

**How long do we store personal data?**

We do not store your data any longer than is strictly necessary to achieve the goals they are collected for. Moreover, you can delete your account if you wish to do so, unless there is still an assignment to be carried out in that you are scheduled for.

If you exercise this right to be forgotten, your profile we be deleted from our platform immediately. All other personal data will be deleted after sending a request by e-mail to [mysteryshopping@secretview.io](mailto:mysteryshopping@secretview.io). All personal data will be deleted within the space of two months unless the data is required to comply with government regulations. With regards to the latter, we maintain a 7-year storage period due to fiscal obligations.

1. **Client contacts**

When we engage in a contract with a new client, we process personal data of the contacts of that client. Both Secret View and the client have a legitimate interest in processing this data because it allows the research(es) to be carried out and the client to use the results to their benefit.

The summary below also applies to those contacts who are themselves (co-)owner of the business we have a contract with.

To that end, we process the following data:

* Name
* Company name
* Phone number
* E-mail address
* Other data that is actively provided by creating a profile, in writing or by phone

**Why do we process personal data?**

We process your personal data to:

\-          Being able to reach an agreement with the client

\-          Communicate with the client (‘s contacts) with regards to the agreement

\-          Handle payments

\-          Analyze user behavior on our website and platform to improve our online tools and to adapt our services to your preferences

\-          Follow up on complaints and questions

\-          Carry out legal duties or court rulings, such as providing data for tax returns

**How long do we store personal data?**

We do not store your data any longer than is strictly necessary to achieve the goals they are collected for.

If you exercise your right to be forgotten, your profile we be deleted from our platform immediately. All other personal data will be deleted after sending a request by e-mail to [support@secretview.io](mailto:support@secretview.io). Once an agreement with a client ends, all personal data will be deleted within the space of three months, unless the data is required to comply with government regulations. With regards to the latter, we maintain a seven-year storage period.

1. **All users**

The following information is applicable to all users in mentioned above.

**Sharing data with third parties**

We never sell personal data to third parties. We will only supply these if it is required to do so in order to carry out the agreement made with the user or to adhere to legal regulations or court rulings. Some parties do receive your personal data and we always sign a processor agreement with these parties to ensure a high standard of protection and confidentiality with regards to your data. We remain responsible for any processing of the data.

The companies we have processor agreements with are:

**BDO**

Address  
Meander 725  
6825 ME Arnhem

Description  
BDO is Secret View’s partner in financial administration and accountancy. They help us to process all payments to mystery shoppers. They receive the following data:

o   Address

o   Bank details

When do they receive this data?  
Only once an actual payment to a person is scheduled, BDO receives these details.

**Exact Online**

Address  
Molengraaffsingel 33  
2629 JD Delft

Description  
Exact Online is the accounting software program Secret View uses to enable payments to community members. Exact Online receives the following data:

o   Address

o   Bank details

When do they receive this data?  
Only once an actual payment to a person is scheduled, Exact Online receives these details.

**Straetus**

Address  
Pollaan 43, 7202BV Zutphen

Description  
Straetus is a collection agency Secret View uses in case of payment issues. Straetus receives the following data:

o   Sex

o   Date of birth

o   Address

o   Phone number

o   E-mail address

o   Location data

o   Bank details

o   Paid amounts, including expenses

When do they receive this data?  
When a mystery shopper has to refund money (for example, when a compensation hsa not fully been spent or the assignment was cancelled) and the money is not refunded. After 45 days, the collection process is transferred to Straetus.

**Microsoft**

Address  
Evert van de Beekstraat 354  
1118 CZ Schiphol

Description  
Microsoft is Secret View’s partner for all data hosting. Microsoft receives the following data (encrypted):

o   Name

o   Sex

o   Date of birth

o   Address

o   Phone number

o   E-mail address

o   Other data that is actively provided by creating a profile, in writing or by phone

o   Personal interests

o   Location details

o   Bank details

o   Payment history

When do they receive this data?  
Microsoft receives this data on a continuous basis in order to store the data safely. The data is encrypted and therefore not accessible to Microsoft.

**CM.com**

Address  
Konijnenberg 30  
4825 BD Breda

Description  
CM.com is Secret View’s partner in communication with community members through WhatsApp. CM.com receives the following data:

o   Name

o   Phone number

When do they receive this data?  
When a registered community member actively agrees to being contacted through WhatsApp in their profile on our platform, this data may be used to contact them through WhatsApp.

**Mollie B.V.**

Address  
Keizersgracht 313  
11016 EE Amsterdam

Description  
Mollie is Secret View’s partner for return payments (unused moneys/cancelled assignments/etc.) from community members to Secret View. Mollie receives the following data:

o   Address

o   Banking details

When do they receive this data?  
In some cases, community members may need to return an amount of money to Secret View due to cancellations, surpluses after assignments, etc. Please find all information on return payments in our Terms & Conditions.

**Mailjet**

Address  
4 rue Jules Lefebvre, 75009 Paris, France

Description  
Mailjet enables Secret View to send newsletters to people registered on our platform.  Mailjet receives the following data:

o   Name                               

o   Email

When do they receive this data?  
When the registered person allows Secret View to use this data for sending newsletters.

**Postmark**

Description  
Postmark enables Secret View to send transactional e-mails (such as ‘Forgot password?’) to people registered on our platform. Postmark receives the following data:

o   Name                               

o   Email

When do they receive this data?  
  
When registering at Secret View. Transactional e-mails are required for the agreement between stakeholders and Secret View.

**Crisp.chat**

Address  
2 Boulevard de Launay, 44100 Nantes, France

Description  
Crisp is a chat tool enabling Secret View to support users of our services. If you are not logged in to our platform, the chat will be anonymized. If you are logged in, Crisp will receive the following data:

o   Name                               

o   Email

When do they receive this data?  
Wanneer de gebruiker zelf de chat opent and is logged in.

**Links**

There may be links in Secret View’s communication channels that we are not owned by us. We are not responsible for the content and privacy protection of the websites behind those links. We strongly advise to read the respective website’s privacy policy.

**Your rights**

You have the right to get insight into your personal data, but also to edit and to delete it. You are free to do so through the personal settings in your account on our platform. Moreover, you have the right to retract your permission to process your personal data or to object to our processing of your data. Also, you have the right to data portability. That means you can ask us to transfer your data in a common format to another organization of your choosing.

Should you like to exercise one or more of these rights, we may ask you to verify your identity via two-factor authentication using e-mail and SMS. You will be sent two codes will have to be verified with Secret View. After this verification, we will grant your request.

We will try to respond as quickly as possible, but within four weeks at the most. We would also like to point out the option of issuing a complaint with the Dutch national authority, the Dutch Data Protection Authority (Autoriteit Persoonsgegevens) through the following link: [https://autoriteitpersoonsgegevens.nl/nl/contact-met-de-autoriteit-persoonsgegevens/tip-ons](https://autoriteitpersoonsgegevens.nl/nl/contact-met-de-autoriteit-persoonsgegevens/tip-ons).

**How we protect personal data**

We take the protection of your personal data very seriously and take fitting measures to prevent and counter abuse, loss, unauthorized access, unwanted publication, and illicit editing of the data.

Please find the most important measures below:

\-          Keeping the online infrastructure updated

\-          Use of security groups

\-          Data encryption

\-          Segmented insight into data

\-          Use of HTTPS in both external and internal communication

\-          Database back-ups

\-          GIT combined with CI/CD for efficient patch management continuation

\-          Stimulating privacy protection awareness with employees

\-          Testing, rating, and evaluating procedures for protective measures

\-          Protocol formulation in case of data leaks or security incidents

\-          Confidentiality agreements

\-          Processor agreements

\-          Minimizing contact with personal data

\-          Keeping track of all data processing activities

\-          Maintaining a data vault

\-          Minimizing reception of personal data by clients

Should you feel your data is not properly protected or there are signs of abuse/misuse of your data, please contact our team at [mysteryshopping@secretview.io](mailto:mysteryshopping@secretview.io).

**Complaints**

You have the right to file a complaint with the Autoriteit Persoonsgegevens (AP) if you feel your data is not being used properly.

**Modifications**

We can always edit this privacy statement, for example in the event of changes in regulation. We advise you to take a look at this statement regularly.

Version July 25, 2023.
